<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Handwritten Digit Recognition Using Tensorflow Keras</title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/post_1_handwritten_using_tensorflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/post_1_handwritten_using_tensorflow/</guid>
      <description>GITHUB: Handwritten Digit Recognition Using Tensorflow Keras link github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loan Approval Machine Learning Logistic Regression</title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/post_2_crm_using_python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/post_2_crm_using_python/</guid>
      <description>GITHUB: Loan Approval Machine Learning Logistic Regression link github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Certification Course (CLF-C01)</title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/blog/post_1_aws_ccp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/blog/post_1_aws_ccp/</guid>
      <description>What is the Certificed Cloud Practitioner (CCP)? The cloud fundamentals e.g. Cloud Concepts, Cloud Architecture, Cloud Deployment Models. AWS Core Services Identity, Security and Governance of the Cloud. Billing, Pricing and Support of AWS Service. AWS Certification Roadmap Beginner Level AWS Certified Cloud Practicioner Associate Level AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate AWS Certified Developer Associate AWS Certified Solution Architect Associate Profesional Level AWS Certified DevOps Engineer Profesional AWS Certified Solution Architect Profesional Specialty Level AWS Certified Security Specialty AWS Certified Advanced Networking Specialty AWS Certified Database Specialty AWS Certified Machine Learning Specialty AWS Certified Data Analytics Specialty Road: CCP -&amp;gt; Solution Architect -&amp;gt; Machine Learning -&amp;gt; Data Analytics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae (CV)</title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:58:38 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>enim ultricies dolore metus ac eiusmod interdum</title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/blog/post_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/blog/post_2/</guid>
      <description>non tempor mauris elementum semper Interdum dolor sit etiam aenean ac fermentum auctor cursus nulla tellus purus justo. Ullamcorper elit do tincidunt auctor sit leo, pulvinar scelerisque do fringilla nisi porttitor fermentum. Tellus elit mauris lobortis iaculis mus morbi nunc lacus. Velit placerat facilisis varius odio purus sociis elementum morbi. Dignissim congue nulla diam aenean mi commodo quisque egestas amet mattis posuere lobortis. Tristique laoreet mus diam tellus vestibulum scelerisque ipsum, rhoncus mollis sed consequat natoque eget sem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>luctus enim ultricies auctor pulvinar nam etiam</title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/blog/post_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/blog/post_3/</guid>
      <description>donec lacinia eleifend sem a Pulvinar tempor ultrices amet praesent aliquet non magnis euismod elit venenatis. Aliqua consequat tristique erat nulla sit risus aliqua posuere. Potenti natoque augue proin accimsan risus scelerisque id integer curabitur mattis amet quisque. Aliquet porta sit sapien natoque sed fringilla, madssa suspendisse vivamus placerat sociis condimentum ridiculus. Natoque egestas non lectus pellentesque nunc mattis eu ridiculus pretium maecenas ligula. Gravida facilisis sem mollis sagittis aliquet ornare bibendum, leo nec morbi tortor diam maecenas tempor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>luctus enim ultricies auctor pulvinar nam etiam</title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/post_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/post_3/</guid>
      <description>donec lacinia eleifend sem a Pulvinar tempor ultrices amet praesent aliquet non magnis euismod elit venenatis. Aliqua consequat tristique erat nulla sit risus aliqua posuere. Potenti natoque augue proin accimsan risus scelerisque id integer curabitur mattis amet quisque. Aliquet porta sit sapien natoque sed fringilla, madssa suspendisse vivamus placerat sociis condimentum ridiculus. Natoque egestas non lectus pellentesque nunc mattis eu ridiculus pretium maecenas ligula. Gravida facilisis sem mollis sagittis aliquet ornare bibendum, leo nec morbi tortor diam maecenas tempor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/handwritten-digits-recognition/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zohansyahfatomi.github.io/projects/handwritten-digits-recognition/readme/</guid>
      <description>handwritten-digits-recognition A script that trains a model to recognize handwritten digits using the MNIST data set. Then it loads external files and uses the neural network to predict what digits they are.
Feel free to add 28x28 pixel images into the digits directory!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
